KEVIN SHAUGHNESSY

Full-Stack Web Developer

Positive detail oriented web developer who is motivated, quick learning, and resourceful. Experience working in and managing teams as well as engaging clients. I have always had a profound interest in programming and decided to take the plunge with General Assembly's immersive to learn the fundamentals.

Work History

2019-12 -Current

General Assembly

Software Engineer Immersive, Boston, MA

- Three-month (600+ hours) of intensive training in a variety of modern programming languages and technologies.
- Covered front and back end programming fundamentals
- Built four web applications from ground up using RESTful APIs I built and integrated data from third party APIs
- Utilized Git/GitHub for version control.

2016-02 -2019-11

Regional Account Manager

Phoenix Group Metals, Phoenix, Arizona

- Developed and managed plans to grow territory across United States and Canada.
- Tracked sales data to assess trends and make proactive strategy changes.
- Managed book of over 40 clients with gross revenue over \$3 million per year.
- Secured high-value accounts through consultative selling, effective customer solutions and promoting compelling business opportunities.

2014-12 -2016-02

Sales

Holloway Mercedes Benz, Manchester, NH

- Delivered high level of assistance by locating products and checking store system for merchandise at other sites.
- Assisted customers with prompt and polite support in-person and via telephone.
- Functioned as backup in areas of sales, support, and services.

Education

2011-09 -2015-05

Bachelor of Science: Business Administration

Southern New Hampshire University - Hooksett, NH

Contact

Address

10 Rose Lane Bedford, NH, 03110

Phone

(603) 361-1424

E-mai

kevinshghnss@gmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/kevin~shaughnessy

Skills

JAVASCRIPT

HTML5

JQUERY

BOOTSTRAP

POSTGRESQL

SQL

EXPRESS.JS

NODE.JS

MONGODB

EMBER.JS

CSS

SASS

AJAX

RUBY ON RAILS

GIT/GITHUB

Languages

Spanish